# JAMES GABRIEL

No154, Itesiwaju Street, Aba aladie, Ayegun, Ibadan Telephone No: 08108685711, 09043198175 Email: younggabmoney@gmail.com

### Personal Profile Statement

I am energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake, or situation that I am presented with, as a graduate with three years working experience in management and engineering field, I am excellent in working with others to achieve a certain objectives on time and with excellent.

## **Achievements**

- Construction of 2.5kva inverter
- Development and Performance Evaluation of 20 mould cylindrical briquetting machine

## Education

- 2019 HSE(Health and Safety Environment) Deeprimex Consulting Grade achieved: Satisfactory
- 2018-2019 HND Mechanical engineering (manufacturing option) The Polytechnic Ibadan
   Grade achieved: UPPER CREDIT
- 2017 WAEC(The West African Examination Council) Brain Builder International College Grade achieved: 6 Distinctions, 2 Credits
- 2015-2016 ND Mechanical engineering The polytechnic Ibadan Grade achieved: UPPER CREDIT
- 2012-2014 NECO(National Examination Council) Dominion College Grade achieved: 9 Credits
- 2009-2011 BECE(Basic Education Certificate Examination)
  Grade achieved: 4 Distinction, 6 Credits
- 2002-2008 FSLC(First School Leaving Certificate Grade achieved: Pass



# **Employment**

- Jan 2019-Present Teacher(Physics, Basic Science, Basic Technology)
  Wemlak High School
- April 2017-Dec 2018 Teacher(Mathematics, Basic Science, Basic Technology)
  Glorious College
- Oct 2015-Feb 2016 Industrial Training(IT) Ministry of Works and Transport Oyo State Secretariat
- Nov 2014-Marc 2015 Student Industrial Work Experience Scheme(SIWES)
  A.G. Leventis Motor
- Aug 2012- July 2014 Sales Manager Logjannock Business Centre
- June 2011-April 2012 Primary School Teacher Rainbow Group of School

#### **SKILLS**

- Enterprise and entrepreneurial skills
- Analytical skills
- Managing ambiguity
- Ability to work under pressure
- Perseverance and motivation
- Leadership skills
- Problem solving
- Teamwork
- Commercial awareness
- Good communication skills

#### **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

In my free time, I like to focus on my sport (table tennis and football), visiting national galleries and meeting new people. I am also very passionate about video gaming and I enjoy travelling out with my friends and family on a regular basis, and I also enjoy reading and blogging

#### REFEREES

#### Rev' Dr Inyang Okon

Proprietor, Logjannock Group of School 08058453264, 09079079940

#### Mrs Glory Magdalene

H.O.D, Bishop Akinyele Grammer School 08074916792, 080809897